Michael A. Armstrong

16 Pleasant St. NY Mills NY 13417

Phone: (315) 807-6475

Email: mikearmstrong2017@gmail.com

Summary

Over 14 years experience delivering outstanding customer service in a variety of settings. Management and supervisory skills to complement a proven ability to make sales. Excellent communicator with an insatiable desire to learn and succeed in any industry.

Work Experience

The Pet Health People, LLC – Brand Ambassador

Jan 2017 – present

- Represent LICKS brand pet nutrition products in Petsmart stores.
- Educate consumers about the brand and its products to grow sales.

Fraccola Enterprises - Store Manager

May 2016 - Dec 2016

- Managed operations at 3 retail stores, including staffing, scheduling, training, generating weekly reports, and bank deposits.
- Installed modern POS systems in 2 stores to improve sales and inventory tracking.
- Improved visibility and sales by utilizing Google and Yelp's business listings.

Salt City Book & Video - Sales Clerk

June 2015 - May 2016

- Assisted customers with product selection and completed sales.
- Received incoming merchandise, stocked sales floor.
- Ensured that sales floor was clean and merchandise properly displayed.

Deaton's Building & Home Center (ACE Hardware) – Dept. Head

Sept 2011 – May 2015

- Utilized my experience with pesticides and power tools to assist customers in the Lawn & Garden Dept.
- Reorganized department and introduced numerous new products.
- Maintained a clean, well-merchandised sales area.
- One of 3 key holders who supervised evening crew until closing.

E-bay seller (Self-employed)

Dec 2010 - Aug 2011

- Accurately described and photographed collectibles for sale.
- Corresponded with potential buyers about merchandise.
- Packed and shipped merchandise to buyers.

Chittenango Landscape – Pesticide Applicator

July 2006 - Dec 2010

- Met with prospective and existing clients to assess needs and recommend solutions.
- Scheduled and delivered exceptional service as contracted.
- Maintained service records in compliance with state and federal regulations.

Genex Cooperative - Breeding Program Specialist

Feb 2003 - July 2005

- Educated prospective clients about advantages of artificial insemination and related services.
- Delivered outstanding service as contracted.
- Maintained accurate records for farm use and for corporate billing.

Education

Oklahoma State University

2000-2002

1989-1991

Coursework in accounting and animal science

Paul Smiths College

Coursework in biology and environmental technology